http://www.masoncontractors.org/privacy/

Fastest Trowel on the Block
Online Auction (see you in 2021)
Dust Extraction Systems
Educational (K-12)
Educational (University)
Stamped Concrete
Stone (Exterior)
Stone (Interior)
Privacy Policy
The Mason Contractors Association of America (MCAA) is committed to protecting your privacy. The MCAA will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and the MCAA is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. The MCAA does not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that has not been outlined in this statement.
Cookies
The MCAA collects cookies on our website to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and the MCAA uses this information only internally - to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. The MCAA does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our website, our product or service check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also change your cookie settings through preferences options in our products and/or services, where applicable.
The MCAA never gives away information about our users. If you choose to email us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, the MCAA will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. The MCAA will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific MCAA product or service.
The MCAA uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.
Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.
Third Parties
The MCAA will not provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. The MCAA will not provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis.
The MCAA may use third party companies to provide delivery of electronic newsletters and other messages over email to subscribers only.
The MCAA does use a third-party advertising company to serve advertisements. The MCAA is not responsible for the content of any third party site that may be linked to from this website.
In conjunction with our in-house advertising, we use third-party advertising companies to place customized advertisements on the pages you view on the Site (eg Google Adsense). Our third-party advertising companies also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to the Site. These companies may use non-personal information collected by the cookies about your visits to the Site and other web sites in order to provide you with advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Security
The MCAA uses precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and your purchases and will never release this information to third parties; however, the MCAA is not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.
All purchases made through the MCAA website are secure and protected.
Obtaining Your Consent
By using the MCAA website, you give the MCAA permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics.
The MCAA may occasionally amend this policy. It is suggested that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time.
Updated: February 21, 2019
“The MCAA has my back on things I could not possibly be doing by myself.”
Mark Kemp
Superior Masonry Builders, Inc.
MCAA member since 1959
Learn More
Together we are stronger
Join the MCAA today
The Mason Contractors Association of America (MCAA) is committed to preserving and promoting the masonry industry by providing continuing education, advocating fair codes and standards, fostering a safe work environment, recruiting future manpower, and marketing the benefits of masonry materials.
Get masonry industry news and information delivered to your inbox.
Subscribe
1481 Merchant Drive     •     Algonquin, IL 60102     •     TF: 800-536-2225     •     P: 224-678-9709     •     F: 224-678-9714Privacy Policy
